▍2026 辛辛那提 ATP1000 半决赛
蒂亚福 7-5 6-3 中岛布兰登 · 赛后场上采访
Francis, congratulations.
祝贺你，蒂亚福
You're back in a Masters 1000 final.
你又打进了大师赛决赛
How does it feel?
感觉怎么样？
It feels pretty damn good.
感觉好极了
Really happy with it.
真的很开心
It's been a great week
这一周很精彩
and a great weekend, unexpectedly,
这个周末也出乎意料
so I'm super happy with it.
我特别满意
Obviously it was a big match tonight.
今晚显然是一场重要的比赛
Were there nerves at the start?
开局的时候紧张吗？
Yeah, I mean, I've been serving horrible.
是啊，我发球一直很糟糕
I mean, I thought I actually came out
不过其实一上场
feeling pretty good.
感觉还不错
I guess I need to pick up my serve better
我得把发球
at the end.
在后段找回来
I got in a good rhythm there at the end.
到最后我找到了节奏
You've coped without the serve,
没有稳定发球
haven't you, so well?
你还是扛住了，是吧？
Yeah, I mean,
是啊
I'm just backing myself with my movement
我更相信自己的脚步
and how I'm hitting the ball from back
还有底线的击球
of the court.
手感
And I'm returning great.
接发球状态也很好
But yeah, it's always good to have some
不过能得到这样
of the approval.
认可，感觉总是很好
Arthur Fils awaits in the final.
决赛等着你的是菲斯
I mean, two showmen, right?
两个都很有表演欲的人
What are you going to deliver for us?
你准备给我们带来什么？
Hell of a show, and hopefully a double W
会有一场好戏
with that.
希望能双赢
He's a hell of a player, moves great,
他是个很强的球员，移动好
serves great.
发球也好
Again, he has shot making.
还有制胜分的手感
He's going to want it. He's going
他会全力以赴
to be pumped up.
会很兴奋
And so am I. I'm excited to face him.
我也是，我很期待和他交手
And yeah, that's the best way to win.
这才是赢球该有的样子
Good luck. Well done tonight.
祝你好运，今晚打得漂亮
Well done.
谢谢